How's your day?
Fine.
- Lots of laundry, huh?
- Yes.
But we're already done.
Just a second.
[murmuring]
Just leave your husband already.
Come with me.
So you can have this anytime.
Really, Olan? At the altar?
You don't have any respect.
Good morning.
I just want to ask,
where is the way to
the top of the mountain?
It's at the end of the crossroads.
On the left, there is a mountain.
On the right, at the top.
Hey!
Your eyes are wild again.
Do you want me
to poke them out?
I'm just appreciating...
The beautiful nature.
Ah!
Hey!
Let's go!
I'm Zak,
and this is Jaz, my girlfriend.
Oh no, love. I'm sorry.
I had something
to take care of.
Oh! Your towel.
Come close,
I'll wipe your sweat.
You removed your towel again.
I told you not to
remove your towel.
Wait a minute.
I'll make you some food.
I really need therapy
so I can walk
and move by myself.
What if...
we continue the massage
Mang Karyo does to me?
What we need to do
is find a therapist for you.
A professional,
that's what the doctor said.
It's expensive.
We're just giving
Mang Karyo a small fee.
He's okay with it.
Nothing is happening
with his massages on you.
What if...
Let’s temporarily pawn this house.
You can't work.
How are we going to pay?
We can't always be like this.
Don't worry about it.
We will figure it out.
Let's go to sleep, love.
Okay.
Ah, excuse me.
Is this the right way
towards the top of the mountain?
Go straight ahead.
It's at the end of the crossroads,
turn right.
You're going up alone?
Yes.
It’s hard to be alone.
You're not with anybody.
It’s lonely.
Oh no!
You might get lost there.
There must be a signage
directing to the top.
I don't know, there
was signage before,
but now I'm not sure.
It's been a while
since I went there.
But just follow that narrow path.
What is that?
Chocolate?
No. It's an energy bar.
That is what I usually eat
when I suddenly get hungry,
especially when I'm at the gym.
And when I go to the mountains.
It's delicious.
You’re carrying a lot.
Are you going to spend
the night there?
Yes, probably.
I'll go ahead.
I think I'm interrupting you.
No, it's okay.
I'm already done.
Thank you.
So, let's go?
What?
I'm going the same way.
By the way, I'm Dolores.
I'm Jayron.
- Let's go?
- Let's go.
Hey,
your next path is to the right.
I’m going this way.
Alright, thank you.
Okay.
Ouch! Ouch!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Sit here first.
- Come.
- Oh.
Where?
- Which part?
- There, right there.
- Here?
- Ouch!
It hurts.
- This?
- Yes! That's it! Keep going!
Are you okay?
Ouch!
Keep going!
Are you okay?
Ah, yes. Thank you!
Ah, let me take you home.
No need, I can manage.
Someone might see us.
Who? No one is here.
Don’t you like me?
Oh, that's not the case.
But...
But what?
I haven't done it before.
With that handsome face of yours?
I don't have any experience.
You haven't had a girlfriend?
I did have a girlfriend...
I haven’t done it
with any of them.
Because for me, I’ll do it only
when I’m ready to marry her.
You're funny.
Dolores.
I'm going to the other town.
I found a job there.
Come with me.
So that you won't get thirsty.
Don't tease me, Olan!
You probably thought I didn’t
know what you’re doing, huh?
Is that why you're always here?
Please, let me have you.
Before I leave.
Maybe you'd like me
to tell your husband
what you've been doing?
I’ve got nothing else to do here
but do laundry, and fetch water!
Really?
Who was the person
I saw the other day?
He just asked me something.
How about us?
Just like that?
Maybe you want me
to go to your husband instead.
We'll catch up.
So, Dolores?
Give me some time to think.
I don't like to wait.
I might not be able
to control myself.
I'll figure it out.
I’ll come to you myself.
Don't worry.
Our savings are running low.
I'll accept more laundry.
Thank you, Dolores.
Until next time.
Here's my payment.
Thank you!
Dolores!
- Ah, hi!
- How did you find my house?
I asked around.
I thought you returned to Manila.
I'm on vacation for
a few more days.
I also rented a
small room in town.
Up for getting lost again?
I kept thinking of you…
guess that’s why I got lost again.
I was hoping to court you.
Can I?
Someone beat you to it.
What?
You already have a boyfriend?
Husband.
Is he there?
Yes, he got into an accident.
He fell off a tree,
that's why he can't walk.
Maybe I can help.
How?
I'm a PT.
Physical Therapist.
That's my job.
Is that so?
Let's go.
Uh... Love?
Someone will be able to help you.
I'm Jayron.
How are you?
I'm Rodel.
I'm a physical therapist from Manila.
I met Dolores at the--
The village.
I saw him talking to the
community watchman
at the village when he went
up the mountain last week.
I overheard that he was a PT,
so...
I asked if he can help you.
I do community work
from time to time.
I help those who need therapy.
Have a seat.
Alright.
Put your bag down.
Okay.
When did your accident happen?
Almost six months already.
I have hypertension.
And then...
I fell from the tree in the backyard.
This is what happened.
You may have kept
the prescription,
medication, or any documents
given by the doctor.
Yes.
I'll get it.
Here.
Lower limb trauma.
Your hips and thighs
are fractured.
I believe you were given
a prescription for the pain.
Did you continue the medication?
Yes.
I followed everything
the doctor told me.
The only thing I haven't
done is the therapy
because we don't
have enough budget.
I can do the therapy for you.
Right?
We don't have any
money to pay you.
Don't think about it.
I'll help you.
Do you want me to check it?
- Okay.
- Alright.
Just a second,
I'll get you something to drink.
I advise that you have
something to hold on to,
like parallel bars or some wood.
Would bamboo be okay?
Yes, anything that
you can hold on to.
Dolores!
I have a lot of bamboo
in our backyard?
We'll have one built.
Ah, yes.
Thank you.
I don't know how to repay you.
I'm doing this for you.
Let's go.
What?
How about Rodel?
You're going up
the mountain, right?
Let's go!
You're coming with me?
How about your husband?
I already cooked our food
for the whole day this morning.
And he can move, just slowly.
I'll come back down
after I drop you off.
Will your husband
be okay with this?
You talk a lot.
Let's go, come this way.
Oh, thank you.
I hope...
What?
I hope you can stay,
but I know you can't.
Do you really think I can
go back at this hour?
What do you mean?
I'll head down tomorrow morning.
How about Rodel?
Don't worry, I'll talk to him.
Alright.
Just tell him you came
with me as a tour guide.
That's too much.
Take it.
I won’t turn this down
because I really need it.
Thank you.
Thank you also
for coming with me.
You look like you’re used
to climbing mountains.
Of course.
I've climbed a lot of mountains.
Are you used to
making girls fall for you?
No, I don't.
It’s always me
who ends up alone.
Why don’t you just give in?
It’s because my
parents are religious.
Everything's forbidden.
No this, no that.
I grew up being told not to sin.
So, what now?
You’ve become a sinner
because you’re into me.
And especially me,
because I gave in.
Seeing Rodel made me think.
I feel the same way.
I started questioning
what I'm doing.
I know it's wrong.
But what should I do?
I also have desires.
Beauty comes with price.
This is your fault.
Why me?
You made me experience
the most passionate sin.
Ah...
Oops!
You can't be too excited.
Oh, I see. I can't get excited--
If you say so, then don't.
I'm serious.
I'm really serious.
I only feel free
when I'm with you.
I feel the same way.
You make me forget
all my problems,
even if just for a little while.
Let’s enjoy this little
forbidden escape.
Uh...
Jayron asked me to be his
tour guide to the mountain.
He even paid me.
He also told me that...
He'll come back every Saturday
and Sunday for your therapy.
[groans]
Ow! That hurts, doc!
Take it easy, please.
Ouch!
Please be gentle!
Must be nice!
Taking all the pleasure
you want, huh?
Talking nonsense again, Olan.
You’ve totally lost it.
If Rodel saw this…
You think he’d be happy?
You bastard! Delete it!
Who's crazy now?
You think I don't know?
Every time a tourist
gets lost in the woods,
you always give them
a different route.
A route
straight to your legs.
I’m begging you, Olan.
Please, delete it.
On one condition.
What do you want?
You know exactly what I want.
Right?
So?
You in?
Did you enjoy?
Just hurry it up, bastard.
Damn you, you delete that!
You think I'm stupid like you?
Why would I delete it if I’m
getting something out of it?
You son of a bitch!
You really are a son of a bitch!
Remember what
I’m about to tell you.
From now on,
you’ll be my slave.
You son of a bitch!
Thanks.
Is it getting hard for you?
You’re the one working for us.
I can't satisfy your
needs anymore.
Do you still love me?
You’re overthinking everything.
Let’s go to sleep.
- Okay, a little more.
- Take it easy.
There you go.
You've got it.
Go for it.
Oh!
There!
You're doing good!
- Here.
- Thank you so much, Doc!
I think you just need
a little more therapy,
and soon you'll get better.
Thank God.
Cook a nice meal, Dolores.
Join us for dinner, Doc.
It’s just Jayron,
and I’m not a doctor.
What do you mean?
You're helping me heal.
Stay for the night, Doc.
It's getting late already.
No, it's okay.
I still have a patient
tomorrow at the hospital.
For therapy as well.
How will you go home then?
I have a car.
I parked it outside.
I was also thinking that
I might get home late.
I see.
Before,
you used to come
in the morning.
I even told Dolores,
maybe you won’t make it today.
Ah, I had to see a
patient at their house,
so I'm a bit late today.
Uh...
Doc?
Can...
Can I ask you something?
Personal?
Ah, personal?
When I
can walk and move
around properly,
will my little one
also get better?
- Rodel, stop it.
- Uh...
Since the accident,
it hasn't stood up.
That condition really
does affect sexual function.
As long as you’re
still feeling pain
and haven’t fully healed,
it can affect your sexual life
because some nerves
aren’t functioning.
Whether erectile dysfunction
will go away and if it will return,
only a doctor can say, but
I think it will work again.
Did you hear that, Dolores?
There’s still hope.
I’ll go ahead.
Doc,
if you really have to go.
Take care,
and I’ll rest as well.
Be careful.
I can manage.
So I can get the hang of it.
Thanks again, Doc!
You're welcome.
Thank for helping me and Rodel.
Please don't get tired of it.
I won't get tired as long
as you want me to.
How can I repay you?
Your love is enough
and seeing you everyday.
Do you really need to leave?
I need to go back to Manila.
What about Rodel?
He won't see us.
And he's already asleep.
Just be careful when
taking your regular walks.
I have something to give you.
This is for you.
Wow!
This must be expensive, Doc.
Oh no. Let me show you.
Try it.
Here.
A friend who is a
supplier gave me that.
It's a sample
to recommend to patients who
are having a hard time walking.
These medicines
are from my friend
that's a doctor,
and these are his prescriptions.
We already owe you so much, Doc.
Don’t worry about that.
What’s important is
that you get better.
Well, I’ll go now.
Rodel, I'll just walk him out.
Alright.
Take care.
Thank you.
Thank you, Doc.
Let's go.
Are there tourists
camping here too?
Yes, during the holidays,
but not a lot of
tourists these days.
What's your plan?
Plan?
Once Rodel fully recovers.
It would be better
so that he can work.
Once he is fully recovered.
How about us?
Us? What do you mean, us?
Us.
Once your husband is better,
will this go on?
I can't say.
You really love him so much?
Yes.
I caught him cheating.
I confronted them.
He came back to his senses.
But maybe the proverb is true.
That no matter how
much you avoid it,
someone will still come.
I guess that's me.
Hmm...
Maybe.
That's why you have tattoos.
This?
This.
This, and here on my side.
Also this?
My piercings?
That was my foolishness
with my first boyfriend.
He really likes tattoos
and piercings.
Well, I loved him.
That's how it is.
It's nice.
You really are something.
Is this your new guy?
Don't you want your
husband anymore?
You're causing trouble even here?
You don’t like being
bothered, do you?
What do you want?
Making you moan?
Stop it already, Olan!
Really, here in the woods?
You really do it here?
Wait a minute, man.
Maybe you're mistaken.
You're not from here,
so don't interfere.
Don't meddle in my life
and my married life.
You're really defending that doctor?
You jerk!
- Stop it already.
- Asshole!
You used to be
the one courting me.
Shut up!
You don’t know what you’re saying—
you’re just drunk!
And I told you,
you’re mine.
What do you want?
Or maybe...
You want me
to show your man
what you’ve been doing?
You’re going crazy, Olan!
You’re losing it!
I’ve been crazy about you
for a long time, Dolores.
This will be fun.
Just like old times.
But what I really want...
Is for your man to watch.
While I'm making you feel good.
Right?
Or maybe
you'd rather we go to Rodel?
And all four of us
share this moment?
You son of a bitch!
Undress!
Move away!
I'll do what you want.
Just don't hurt us.
Move away!
Undress!
Don't come any closer!
Stop it!
Get naked!
Want me to shoot
you in the head?
Don't come closer!
Undress! Come on!
I am! I am!
Don't come closer!
Please, stop this.
Faster! I'm waiting!
Lie down!
You're so annoying!
Jayron!
Do you want to join?
What?
You want to?
Watch!
Don't come any closer.
Olan!
Have mercy!
I said, be quiet!
Want me to shoot
you in the head?
Rodel!
I saw everything.
I didn't stop you because
I love you that much.
I wasn't expecting that
we’d end up like this.
I want you
to be happy.
I had a feeling you had
something with Jayron for a while.
I just want to say goodbye.
I submitted my
application to Canada.
I got approved.
I’ll go back to Manila to...
Fix my documents.
I admit that I was wrong.
I hope you can forgive me.
Especially you, Rodel.
Goodbye.
Sorry.
Doc!
For everything that happened.
Can we...
Can we forget everything?
Life is tough.
When we carry so much.
Wherever you may end up,
don’t forget about us.
For all of your help,
thank you so much.
Thank you.
Take care.
Take care of Rodel.
He's a really a good person.
You're really lucky
to have Rodel,
who truly loves you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
But I love my husband more.
I can't leave him.
For the short time
I’ve known you,
I loved you.
Whatever help I can give,
just contact me.
I won’t forget you.
Always take care.
Always remember,
there was a Jayron
who courted you
but fell in love.
I love you, even
though I shouldn’t.
Let’s not lose our
way again, okay?
Come on,
let’s go inside and eat.